<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Nikul Patel&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Nikul Patel&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 22:08:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dotfiles</title>
      <link>/projects/dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>Dotfiles&gt; Dotfiles # Here are my configuration files for Neovim and Fish shell.
These are a work in progress, but already give a decent text editor/terminal setup.
Why not &amp;hellip;&gt; Why not &amp;hellip; # I still use other tools, but I mainly use Neovim for coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science</title>
      <link>/projects/data_science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 22:10:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/data_science/</guid>
      <description>Below are links to various Data Science projects I&amp;rsquo;ve done over the past few years.
Title Description Link Credit Modelling Model credit loan defaults using decision trees Link Crypto Forecasting Predict intraday Crypto returns using ML models (Kaggle Competition) Link ONS Housing Data Use publicly available data from the ONS to investigate what drives rental yields Link Car Dataset Exploration Finding ways to suitably interpolate missing data on this dataset about vehicles Link (Note: I only recently pushed these so some of the commit timestamps are inaccurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animated  Background</title>
      <link>/projects/website_background/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 16:03:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/website_background/</guid>
      <description>I used VantaJS + a Hugo partial template to add this animated birds background to my website.
Hugo (the static site generator I&amp;rsquo;m using) allows for extensive customisation. Depending on the theme you&amp;rsquo;re using (I&amp;rsquo;m using Blowfish) you can add custom HTML to your website using a Hugo template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homepage Quotes</title>
      <link>/projects/homepage_quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:03:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/homepage_quotes/</guid>
      <description>I was interested in learning how to use Hugo&amp;rsquo;s shortcodes to add JavaScript to my website to make it less boring.
I wrote a Goodreads quote scraper so a natural idea was to print random quotes on the homepage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quote Scraper</title>
      <link>/projects/quote_scraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 20:46:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/quote_scraper/</guid>
      <description>I was interested in learning more about the Go programming language so I wrote a short script in Go to scrape quotes from Goodreads.
You can find the code here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>/projects/this_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:12:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/this_website/</guid>
      <description>How this was Built&gt; How this was Built # Frameworks&gt; Frameworks # The website is built using HUGO, a static site generator written in Go. Hugo has a few features I like:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
